{
    "subject": "resource/Atari_7800",
    "predicate": "ontology/type",
    "object": "resource/Home_video_game_console",
    "human_readable": "The Atari 7800 is a home video game console.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9160181879997253,
            "question": "How did the Atari 7800 influence future home video game consoles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8331816792488098,
            "question": "What type of device is the Atari 7800?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7982234954833984,
            "question": "Is there a resurgence of interest in vintage Atari games and consoles like the 7800?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7226349711418152,
            "question": "What was the Atari 7800 primarily used for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6989663243293762,
            "question": "What were some popular games released for the Atari 7800?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6265392899513245,
            "question": "What company manufactured the Atari 7800?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6191202998161316,
            "question": "When was the Atari 7800 released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.535959780216217,
            "question": "What features made the Atari 7800 unique?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47072017192840576,
            "question": "Was the Atari 7800 successful in the market?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37775787711143494,
            "question": "How did the Atari 7800 compare to its predecessors?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Atari 7800 is a home video game console.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4192_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was the Atari 7800 successful in the market?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4192_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What features made the Atari 7800 unique?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4192_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was the Atari 7800 released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4192_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4192_127.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4192_135.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4192_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4192_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4192_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4192_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4192_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4192_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4192_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4192_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references that confirm the Atari 7800 ProSystem (or simply the Atari 7800) is a home video game console, released by Atari Corporation in 1986 as a successor to previous consoles."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}